momastery.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Statement Last updated: May 25, 2018 1.

                                Privacy Statement
Last updated: May 25, 2018
    1. ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS
Momastery, LLC (“Company”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This
Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the
information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website(s).
By accessing www.momastery.com and any other Company websites (this
“website”), you acknowledge and fully understand Company’s Privacy
Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices
described in this Privacy Statement.
    2. PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES
Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor
sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the
corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and
others who participate in Company services are encouraged to participate in
industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer
privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or
practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not
responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend
and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and
other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete
any transaction with such parties.
    3. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT
Company collects certain information from and about its users three ways:
directly from our web server logs, cookies, the user, including in response to
surveys and questionnaires and content voluntarily shared in forums.
a. Web Server Logs.
When you visit our website, we may track information to administer the site
and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:
      Your Internet protocol address.
      The kind of browser or computer you use.

       Number of links you click within the site.
       State or country from which you accessed the site.
       Date and time of your visit.
       Name of your Internet service provider.
       Web page you linked to our site from.
       Pages you viewed on the site.
b. Use of Cookies
Company or its third party email marketing service vendor may use cookies to
personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is
placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run
programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to
you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie
to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to
save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a
site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent
visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases
site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information
as well as providing personalized functionality.
Company reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner
companies, and to allow other companies to place cookies on our website to the
extent required for the performance of such partner’s services for Company or
to the extent there is an overriding customer value associated with such cookie
use (such as merging into momastery.com a site that relies on third-party
cookies).
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers
automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings, then
be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our website.
c. Personal Information of Users
Visitors to our website may be permitted to register for certain services such as
a newsletter. When you register, we will request some personal information
such as name, address, email, telephone number or facsimile number, account
number and other relevant information.

We will not disclose personal information we collect from you to third parties
without your permission except to the extent necessary including:
      To fulfill your service requests for products or services.
      To protect ourselves, our customer or our vendors from liability or to
       defend our rights, including investigations of fraud or misconduct.
      To third parties who have agreed in writing to maintain such information
       in confidence and use such information solely in performance of services
       to us.
      To respond to legal process or comply with law, including subpoenas.
      To entities under common ownership or control with us or to our owners,
       or
      In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.
How              do           I          withdraw            my          consent?
If after you opt-in or after having not initially taken an opportunity to opt-out,
you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you,
for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time,
by contacting us at contact@momastery.com. If you exercise this option, you
agree that you will no longer be entitled to use or have access to Company’s
websites or the services we provide.
Company reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor the user content
you post on Momastery.org and any of our social media sites. We reserve the
right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason,
including without limitation if in our sole opinion such information or material
violates, or may violate, any applicable law or to protect or defend our rights or
property or those of any third party. Company also reserves the right to remove
information upon the request of any third party.
    4. DO NOT TRACK
Some browsers provide the ability to send a Do Not Track signal to websites.
Company websites do not respond to these signals or similar mechanisms.
    5. HOW TO CORRECT,                   UPDATE,       OR     DELETE       YOUR
       INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information
we store about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information,
contact us at contact@momastery.com.
    6. HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION
We use commercially reasonable procedures to protect the personal
information that we collect from you against loss, theft and misuse, as well as
unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. No security system
is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases or the
security during transmission to us of the information you supply over the
Internet. You can help us by taking precautions to protect your personal
information when you are on the Internet and only disclose information that
you want made public. Change your passwords often using a combination of
letters and numbers and make sure to use a secure web browser.
For the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement, personal information may
be transferred to, processed, stored and accessed by us, our affiliates and third
parties in the United States and in other jurisdictions where we or they operate.
Courts and other authorities in these jurisdictions may, in certain
circumstances, be entitled to access your personal information. By using the
website, you consent to this transfer, processing, storage and access of your
personal information in and/or outside of the jurisdiction in which you reside.
    7. AGGREGATE DATA
We may share and publicize aggregate and/or de-identified information shared
with third parties and the public.
    8. CHILDREN UNDER 16
We do not specifically market to or knowingly collect personal information from
children under 16 for marketing purposes. Because some information is
collected online, it may not appear to be the personal information of a child
under 16. If a child under 16 submits personal information to us and we learn
that the personal information is the information of a child under 16, we will
attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. If you are under 16, please
do not register for any of our services or provide us any information about
yourself (such as your name, email address or phone number).
    9. CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT

As required by the California Online Privacy Protection Act (“California Act”)
and the California Business and Professions Code, this Privacy Statement
identifies the categories of personally identifiable information that we collect
through our website about individual consumers who use or visit our website
and the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom such personally
identifiable information may be shared.
Depending on the visitor’s activity at our website, certain “personally
identifiable information” (as that term is defined in the California Act) may be
collected, in addition to information set forth in other sections of this document.
For purposes of the California Act, the term “personally identifiable
information” means individually identifiable information about an individual
consumer collected online by us from an individual and maintained by us in an
accessible form, and may include any of the following: (1) a first and last name;
(2) a home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city
or town; (3) an email address; (4) a telephone number; (5) any other identifier
that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual; and (6)
information concerning a user that the web site collects online from the use,
and maintains in personally identifiable form, in combination with an identifier
described within this Privacy Statement.
   10.CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT
Company has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement.
When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy
page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay
informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we
collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this
privacy statement and any updates.
   11. TRANSLATIONS
This Privacy Statement is executed in English. You agree and acknowledge that
you have reviewed this Privacy Statement in English. To the extent that any
translations of this Privacy Statement are provided, they are solely for
convenience and is of no binding effect. The English language version of this
Privacy Statement shall control.
   12. CONTACTING US

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation,
failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please
contact us at contact@momastery.com.
Company will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and
resolve any problem or question.
